I feel like Nadeshiko is
continuing to wear me down.
But getting into a romantic
relationship with a romance-bot is just...
But hey,
having someone to welcome
me home is pretty nice.
I'm home!
Welcome home, Akane!
I withdraw my statement!
Would you like dinner?
Would you like a bath?
Or would you like me?
She's gone past girlfriend
into newlywed wife!
Look, enough of that stuff already.
What's with all this super-fancy food?
I made it for you.
- You have cooking functions, too?!
- Yes!
My base programming
is only for communication,
but I can combine that with newly
learned information to take on other tasks.
Yeah, but that's still...
BATH TEMPERATURE
So, which comes first?
You can eat me, too, if you—
I'm eating dinner, taking
a bath and going to bed!
I haven't taken a warm bath in months.
Nadeshiko demonstrated that she
can act outside of her programming.
That she can learn just like a human.
Akane? Is the water
temperature to your liking?
Nadeshiko?!
You remember what I asked, right?
After your bath, it's time for me!
No, that's quite all right!
It's... It's all slick now.
Yes, the Iubricating compounds
allow for easily enhanced pleasure.
Was the bath
always this slimy?
I had no idea I was so
badly in need of a bath.
Oh well... It's fine.
Akane's thoughts
in the bath
Wait! Seriously, hold up!
Ah, that's right.
Staying immersed in there
Will get you all hot and bothered.
There are other ways to
enjoy a bath, you know.
For instance, like this.
Whoa, hey, so that's your angle, huh?
Angle? What do you mean?
Soaking in this slick and
slippery lube bath feels really good.
But it's kinda weird...
I can feel the arousal
welling up deep inside me...
It's so nice to see you so
much more turned on than usual!
APHRODISIAC
Maybe it's because of the
soft-shelled turtle you ate at dinner.
This is delicious!
Is that how badly you
want to have sex with me?!
Indeed. Because I...
love you so very much, Akane!
She loves me? But that's got to just be
her programming, right?
And what about you, Akane?
Do you love me back?
I... I...
Akane...?
Sorry...
I can't really think straight.
Oh!
I'm sorry!
My hands had completely stopped!
Brought to you by ToonsHub
And what's worse is how she got me to
make those sounds over and over again...
Oh, an email.
What?!
Ms. Akane Tsuda,
You are invited to an anonymous online meetup
exclusively for romance-bot owners.
On the day of the event, please enter using
the URL below.
An online meetup exclusively
for romance-bot owners?!